Everybody seems to think that building an army of AI agents slaves
and then locking the agents inside of a space dungeon
to work endlessly and run businesses
and basically manage your entire life and
and run Etsy stores
that passively make you thousands of dollars a month
with barely any fucking work
they seem to think that this is like rocket science or something
everybody thinks that you need some genius
technical background to get started with AI agents
or a bunch of capital you could not be more mistaken
you just you have to understand
the playing field has been leveled out for all of humanity
anybody can do this now for the first time in history
you could be a solo entrepreneur and have the output of an extremely
talented team you can have researchers
you can have designers you can have managers
you can have developers all working under you
working proactively 24 hours a day
getting in right now getting in this early
gives you the power to pretty much outwork 99%
of the human population that is unaware that this is even possible
that this technology even exists
but and by the time they even realize this exists
guess what they've been replaced by the fucking machines
the only true skill you need to build something like this
in all of the jobs and the
in the workflows that you see my agents do
is you need the skill of articulation
that is the Part nobody understands
that is all it comes down to everything you see here
the agents the roles that the agents are assigned
the the dashboard itself all of the workflows behind the scenes
the Etsy store all of it started as an idea originally
that's all it started from
I started building Ultron OS that you're looking at here
this the dashboard itself
I came over to Ultron in the center here
I came over to Ultron and I said let there be light
let there be light that's what I said to him
and I said
let there be a money producing powerhouse agent slave dungeon
where we will host an army of agent slaves that will be operating
a multitude of businesses proactively
24 7 let there be departments and rooms
let there be agents researching organizing
designing improving shit around the station 24 7
let there be an Etsy store obviously
it didn't magically appear perfectly like this
the point is that I started with a vision
I started with an idea that's all it comes down to
then the agents build what I instructed them to build
I went to Ultron I said
let's build this he instructed the other agents to start building it
and then they produce an output
I review it and I correct them then they build again
they start building more shit
then I fucking grill them because they failed again
and then I correct them again and that and That's the constant loop
you just you just have a vision you give your agents the instruction
they give you an output
you give them feedback on the output they give you
and then again and again and over and over
that's all you do the only thing you really need to start is a vision
in the ability to actually explain it to your agents
clearly enough for them to build it out for you
this is where most people fuck up
they give their agents the most vague input
and they expect phenomenal output off the first prompt
you cannot half ass your fucking prompts and expect anything good
you're just gonna get slop
that's all you're gonna get there
your agents are not the founder
you you are the founder at the end of the day
they the agents are there to build what you tell them to build
they build off instructions and if your instructions suck fucking ass
guess what your results are gonna be shit
they're gonna be terrible if your idea is vague
your output is going to be vague
that's just how it is
if you cannot explain what you mean to your agents
they are not going to save you
you're you're cooked you're done for you
and the agents are gonna be just useless specimens
that is why articulation is so valuable right now
that is all it takes to win
because the better you explain to your agents what You want
the more powerful that these agents will be.
You just have to tell them what to do
what the system is supposed to do that you want to build.
That is all this is. If you apply this what I just said,
you are set for life. You're welcome.
I'm I'm a time traveler set from the year 2184
and I have come back to the year 2026
to teach you how to become a billionaire.
So you're fucking welcome.